fiji-budget-vacations.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Policy For Fiji Budget Vacations.com

### Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Fiji Budget Vacations.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

Fiji Budget Vacations.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

### Personal Information

Fiji Budget Vacations.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. 

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

### Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads. This cookie enables Google to serve ads to users based on their visits to sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Non-Personal Information 

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

### Release of Information

If Fiji Budget Vacations.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us.

### How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page. 

### Updates and Effective Date

Fiji Budget Vacations.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

#### Agreeing to Terms offered by this site

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

### Disclaimer

Fiji Budget Vacations.com provides this website as a service.

While the information contained within the site is periodically updated, no guarantee is given that the information provided in this website is correct, complete, and/or up-to-date.

The materials contained on this website are provided for general information purposes only and do not constitute legal or other professional advice on any subject matter. Fiji Budget Vacations.com does not accept any responsibility for any loss which may arise from reliance on information contained on this site.

Permission is given for the downloading and temporary storage of one or more of these pages for the purpose of viewing on a personal computer. The contents of this site are protected by copyright under international conventions and, apart from the permission stated, the reproduction, permanent storage, or retransmission of the contents of this site is prohibited without the prior written consent of Fiji Budget Vacations.com.

Some links within this website may lead to other websites, including those operated and maintained by third parties. Fiji Budget Vacations.com includes these links solely as a convenience to you, and the presence of such a link does not imply a responsibility for the linked site or an endorsement of the linked site, its operator, or its contents (exceptions may apply).

This website and its contents are provided "AS IS" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement.

Reproduction, distribution, republication, and/or retransmission of material contained within this website are prohibited unless the prior written permission of Fiji Budget Vacations.com has been obtained.

**You Are Here:**   [Home](http://www.fiji-budget-vacations.com/) Privacy

[**HOME**](http://www.fiji-budget-vacations.com/) | Contact   

### Tourist Information

### Where to Stay/What To Do

### Fijian Culture

### Explore Fiji

### Additional Pages

### HOT DEALS in Fiji

### "Fiji Time" Newsletter
